Guide to the Fritz Leiber Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Writings
  - The Doll House (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Dr. Dragonet's Psionic Elixir (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Endfray of the Ofay (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Endfray of the Ofay - Introduction (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Enormous Bedroom (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - The Enormous Bedroom - Rejections (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Enslaved Human Brains of Tomorrow/Snaring the Human Mind (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Enzenbacher's Eight Norse Gods (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Ervool (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fafhrd and Me (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fafhrd and the Grey Mouser Book 1 - Author's introduction (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fantasy: Many Mansions and Hovels (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fantasy Newsletter "On Fantasy", Sept. 1979-Aug. 1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fantasy World - A Few Fafhrd and Mouser Firsts (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Fish Stew in Its Infinite Varieties (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Four Windows (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Frights: Wonder and Terror - Introduction (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Fritz Leiber: A Bibliography, 1969-1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The First Monstreme (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Game for Motel Room (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The Ghost Light (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Glory of Tros (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - The Glove (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Gonna Roll the Bones (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Good, New Days (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Grandmaster (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
  - Gray Magic (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - The Great Baron (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Great Day Coming or, It Came and Went (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - The Great San Francisco Glacier (Box 28, Folder 11-15)
  - Grettir's Fight with Glam (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - The Gulliver Chapter (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Hamlet (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - The Hatchery of Dreams (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Henrik Ibsen: Apocryphal Prophet (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - A Hitch in Space (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Homes for Man in the Stars (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Horrible Bedroom (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Horrible Imaginings (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - How to Live with Machines (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Hurricane Horror (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - In the Sunlight (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - John Carter: Sword of Theosophy (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - The Juice Head Murders (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Julius Caesar (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Kindergarten (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Knight's Move (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Kreativity for Kats (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Last (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - The Leaders (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Lie Still, Snow White (Box 29, Folder 20-22)
  - Like Son, Like Father (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - The Literature of Cosmic Dread (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - The Lotus Eaters (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Love Letters or, Diplomatic Official Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Lovecraft Story (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Macbeth (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Man Looks at Himself (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Man Who was Married to Space and Time (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Market and Writer's Mind (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Mer-she (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - A Mercedly Short Incident (Box 30, Folder 10-11)
  - The Merchant of Venice (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Metaphysics and the Immediate (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Midnight and the Mirror World (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Midnight by the Murphy watch (Box 30, Folder 15-17)
  - The Mighty Tides (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Moment of Fear: Conjure Wife (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Moon Duel (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - The Moon Porthole (Box 30, Folder 21-22)
  - Moons and Stars and Stuff (Box 30, Folder 23-30)
  - A More Northern Derleth (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - The Mouser Goes Below (Box 31, Folder 2-4)
  - The Mouser on Games (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Adams' Garden of Evil (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Mutterings from Underground (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - My Correspondence with Lovecraft (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - My Life and Writings (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mysterious Doings in the Metropolitan Museum (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mysterious Islands (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mystery of the Japanese Clock (Box 31, Folder 12-15)
  - Myths My Great-Granddaughter Taught Me (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Nature Lover (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - New Fantasy Films (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - New Purposes for Mankind (Box 32, Folder 3-4)
  - Night Passage (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Nor Help for Pain (Box 32, Folder 5a)
  - Not Much Disorder and Not So Early Sex (Box 32, Folder 6-8)
  - Of Dream and Accomplishment (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - On Fantasy (Box 32, Folder 10-16)
  - On Fantasy - Lost Fantasies (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - On Fantasy - My Life and Writings (Box 32, Folder 18-19)
  - On Fantasy - A Night Orgy (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - On Fantasy - An Obsession with the Weird (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - On Fantasy - Sex and the Fantasist: II (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Operation Redemption (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Our Lady of Darkness (Box 32, Folder 24-26)
  - Pale, Brown Thing - Part I (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - Pale, Brown Thing - Synopsis of Part I (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Pale, Brown Thing - Part II (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - Poor Superman (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - The Princess in the Tower 250,000 Miles High (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - The Project that Haunted Me for 15 Years (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Quicks around the Zodiac (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
  - The Repair People (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - The Red Headed Nightmare (Box 33, Folder 12-15)
  - Replacement for Wilmer (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Replacement for Wilmer: A Ghost Story (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Return of the Demon or, Do You Know Dave Wenzel? (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Richmond, Late September (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Rooftop Astronomy or, A Writer's Darkside (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - The Road to Jordan (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Saga of Fafhrd and the Gray Mouser, Book I - Author's introduction (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Saga of Fafhrd and the Gray Mouser, Book II - Author's introduction (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Saga of Fafhrd and the Gray Mouser, Book IV - Author's introduction (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - The Sails of Fancy (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - San Francisco, This Writer's Town (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco's Resident Detective (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Satellite Brat (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Science and the Judo Chop (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Sea Magic (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - The Second Book of Fritz Leiber (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - The Secret Songs (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Shall We Take a Stroll? (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Sheer Magic (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ship of Shadows (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
  - Ships to the Stars (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Silver Eggheads (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - The Sinful Ones. Afterword (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Skinny's Wonderful (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - The Sky is Round (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Stars in Our Neighborhood (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - The Spider (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - The Square (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - The Square Root of Brain (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
  - Stonehenge 94101 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Success (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Sunk Without a Trace (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Table of Contents, Copyright (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Swords and Ice Magic (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Sadness of the Executioner (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Beauty and the Beasts (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Trapped in Shadowland (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - The Bait (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Under the Thumb of the Gods (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Trapped in the Sea of Stars (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - The Frost Monstreme (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Swords and Ice Magic - Rime Isle (Box 34, Folder 30-31)
  - Swords and Lankhmar (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Tale of the Grain Ships (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Tale of the Grain Ships - Prologue (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Tale of the Grain Ships (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
  - Tales of Tomorrow - The Moon is Green (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Tarzan's Long Shadows (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - The Terror From the Depths (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Terror, Mystery, Wonder (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
  - Things I Thought in 1970 I'd Never Live to See (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - The Third Cat (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Alice and the Allergy (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Black Glass (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Black Ewe (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Button Molder (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Casket-Demon (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Cry Witch! (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Deadly Moon (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Death of Princes (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Do You Know Dave Wenzel? (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Eeriest Ruined Dawn World (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - The Glove (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Horrible Imaginings (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - In the X-ray (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Mr. Bauer and the Atoms (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Thirteen Dark Dreads - Rite of Spring (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - The Thirteenth Step (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Those Crazy Foreign Words I (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
  - Those Fish-Hook Fenders (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Those Wild Alien Words II (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Through Hyperspace with Brown Jenkins (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Time and Nth Dimensions (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - To Arkham and the Stars (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - To the End of Time (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Torch - Afterword (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Trapped in the Sea of Stars (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Trapped in the Shadowlands (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - The Tree (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Triweekly Star Guide (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - The Turned Off Heads (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Two-Way Circuit (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Under the Thumbs of the Gods (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - The Undying Creature - Introduction (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Uranus Jam? (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Vanish Enchantress! (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - The Velvet Duchess (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Waif (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - The Walk to Emmaus (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - The Wanderer (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Wargames Old and New (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Wargaming Old and New (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Weird and Wonderful (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Weird Tales - Love at a Distance (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - What's He Doing in There (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - When Brahma Wakes (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - When the Change Winds Blow (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - While Set Fled (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - The Whisperer Re-Examined (Box 36, Folder 34-35)
  - The Wind and Rain Country (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - The Winter Flies (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - The World of Fritz Leiber - Introduction (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - The World of Friz Leiber - Table of Contents (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Introduction (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Hatchery of Dreams (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Goggles of Dr. Dragonet (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Far Reach to Cygnus (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Night Passage (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Nice Girl with Five Husbands (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - When the Change Winds Blow (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - 237 Talking Statues, Etc. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - The Improper Authorities (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Our Saucer Vacation (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Pipe Dream (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - What's He Doing in There? (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Friends and Enemies (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - The Last Letter (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Endfray of the Ofay (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Cyclops (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Mysterious Doings in the Metropolitan Museum (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - The Bait (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - The Lotus Eaters (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Waif (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Myths My Great-Granddaughter Taught Me (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Catch that Zeppelin! (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Worlds of Fritz Leiber - Last (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - X Marks the Red X-ing (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - You're Dreaming Now (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Poetry - The Beach at Santa Monica from Venice to Malibu (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Poetry - Sonnet or, Santa Monica Beach at Sunset (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Poetry - Sonnets to Jonquil and All (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Poetry - The Voice of Man (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Poetry (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Publications
  Tear sheets or full issues of periodicals containing Fritz Leiber's work. Arranged alphabetically by publication title, then by story or article title. Photocopies may have been substituted when original was too fragile to use.
  - (unknown) - The Beach at Santa Monica (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - (unknown) - Black has Its Charms (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - (unknown) - The Inner Circles (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - (unknown) - The Man Who was Married to Space and Time (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - (unknown) - My Correspondence with Lovecraft (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - (unknown) - Myths my Great-Granddaughter Taught Me (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - (unknown) - The Spider (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - (unknown) - Strolling the Banks of the Mainstream (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - (unknown) - Waif (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - 13 Above the Night - Nice Girl with 5 Husbands (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - An ABC of Science Fiction - X Marks the Pedwalk (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Amazing Science Fiction Stories 50th Anniversary - The Death of Princes (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Amazing Stories - Far Reach to Cygnus (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Amazing Stories - Let Freedom Ring (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
  - Amazing Science Fiction Stories - The Death of Princes (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Amazing Science Fiction Stories - Night of the Long Knives (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Arkham Sampler - Fantasy on the March (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - Business of Killing (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - Destiny Times Three (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - The Enchanted Forest (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - The Lion and the Lamb (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - The Mutant's Brother (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - Thought (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - Try and Change the Past (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Astounding Science Fiction - Wanted: An Enemy (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Avon - The Girl with the Hungry Eyes (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Avon 10 Story Fantasy - Cry Witch! (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - The Best of Fritz Leiber - (Cover only) (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - The Best of Omni Science Fiction - The Man Who was Married to Space and Time (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Broadside - Knight to Move (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - California Chess Reporter - The Knight (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Carl Jacobi: An Appreciation - A More Northern Derleth (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Chess Review - The Moriarty Gambit (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - The Churchman (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Crossroads in Time - The Mutant's Brother (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - The Dark Barbarian - Howard's Fantasy (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - The Dark Brotherhood and Other Pieces - Through Hyperspace with Brown Jenkin (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Datebook - Wargames (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Death (Cover only) (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Destiny Times Three (Cover only) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Destiny Times Three (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - The Dragon - The Childhood and Youth of the Gray Mouser (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine - The Number of the Beast (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Escapade - The Night He Cried (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Esquire - To Make a Roman Holiday (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Fandom Unlimited (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Fantastic - Damnation Morning (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Fantastic - I'm Looking for Jeff (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Fantastic - Monsters and Monster Lovers (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Fantastic - Richmond, Late September (Cover only) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Fantastic Adventures - The Ship Sails at Midnight (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Fantastic Adventures - You're All Alone (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Fantastic Science Fact and Fiction Universe - Our Saucer Vacation (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Fantastic Science Fiction Stories - Rats of Limbo (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Fantastic Stories - The ship sails at midnight (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination (Cover only) (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - Adept's Gamble (Cover only) (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - A Bit of the Dark World (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - The Goggles of Dr. Dragonet (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - Hatchery of Dreams (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - The Lords of Quarmall (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - Midnight in the Mirror World (Box 40, Folder 23-24)
  - Fantastic Stories of Imagination - The Unholy Grail (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Fantastic Universe - Time (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Fantasy Literature: A Core Collection and Reference Guide - "Leiber, Fritz" (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Fantasy Newsletter - On Fantasy (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Fantasy World 3 - A Few Fafhrd and Mouser Firsts (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Far Boundaries - Later Than You Think (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - The Fiend in You - The Thirteenth Step (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Folio - The Big Engine (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Fortune Magazine - Mirror (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Fritz Leiber [Sr.]: The Greatest American Interpreter (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Future Combined with Science Fiction Stories - Martians, Keep Out (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Future Fiction - They Never Came Back (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Galaxy - A Bad Day for Sales (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Galaxy - The Creature from Cleveland Depths (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Galaxy - The Crystal Prison (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Galaxy Magazine - The Big Engine (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Galaxy Magazine - Black Corridor (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Galaxy Magazine - The Creature from Cleveland Depths (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Galaxy Magazine - The Good New Days (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Galaxy Reader of Science Fiction - Coming Attraction (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Appointment in Tomorrow (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Bullet with his Name (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Coming Attraction (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - It's Later Than You Think (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - The Moon is Green (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Nice Girl with 5 Husbands (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - A Pail of Air (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Time in the Round (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - What's He Doing in There (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Galaxy Science Fiction - Yesterday House (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Gamma - Crimes Against Passion (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Great Science Fiction from Fantastic - Damnation Morning (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - The Green Millenium (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Gummitch and Friends - (Dust jacket only) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Horror Monster - Burn, Witch, Burn (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Infinity Science Fiction - Friends and Enemies (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Lankhmar: City of Adventure (Game book) (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - LOCUS - Moons and Stars and Stuff (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - LOCUS - Enzenbacher's Eight Norse Gods (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Luna - The Jet Propelled Apocalypse (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction (Cover only) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - 237 Talking Statues, Etc. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Big Holiday (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Big Trek (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - A Deskful of Girls (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Game for Motel Rooms (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Kindergarten (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Last (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Lotus Eaters (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Mutterings from the Underground (Box 41, Folder 20-21)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Myths My Great-Granddaughter Taught Me (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Oldest Soldier (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Pale Brown Thing (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Rump Titty Titty Tum Tah Tee (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Secret Songs (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Ship of Shadows (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - The Silence Game (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - Success (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction - When the Last Gods Die (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Marvel Science Fiction - Should Population Be Controlled? Yes (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Mike Shayne Mystery Magazine - Scream Wolf (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Mike Shayne Mystery Magazine - A Visitor from Back East (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - The Mystery of the Japanese Clock (Galleys) (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - New Purposes (Box 41, Folder 35-36)
  - New Purposes - Casper Scatterday's Quest (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - New Purposes - Nibblings (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - New Worlds - The Square Root of Brain (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Night's Black Agents - Diary in the Snow (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Night's Black Agents - Foreword (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Night's Black Agents - The Man Who Never Grew Young (Box 41, Folder 42-43)
  - Original Science Fiction Stories - Femmequin (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Playboy - All the Weed in the World (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Quicks around the Zodiac (Galleys) (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Rod Serling's Triple W: Witches, Warlocks, and Werewolves - Hatchery of Dreams (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Rogue - The House of Mrs. Delgato (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Rogue - The Spider (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - The Saint Mystery Magazine - Schizo Jimmie (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - The San Francisco Sunday Examiner: California Living - Stalking Sam Spade (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Satellite - Psychosis from Space (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Science Digest - Atom Dust Weapon (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Science Digest - Better Electric World Coming (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Science Digest - Galaxies in Collision (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Science Digest - Hottest and Coldest Molecules (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Science Digest - Man Looks at Himself (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Science Digest - New Tricks with Strange Metals (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Science Digest - Peril at Twice Sound's Speed (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Science Digest - That Dangerous Habit Eating (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Science Digest - Topsy Turvy Land Inside the Atom (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Science Digest - U.S. Reveals Atom Secrets (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Short Stories for Men - Ms. Found in a Maelstrom (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Something about Cats - A Literary Copernicus (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - The Spectator - North Beach (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Star Science Fiction Stories - The Night He Cried (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Starlog - Lankhmar Nights (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Startling Stories - The Black Ewe (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Swords and Deviltry (Cover only) (Box 42, Folder 17)